welcome back my name is D Grant and we
are going through presentations for man
life insurance this is actually fifth um
presentation on manual life insurance
okay manual life insurance supposed to
represent the employees for short-term
disability but actually um we're doing
this in favor of B Mobility we the
employees um were not really benefiting
much at all okay um I can speak for
myself but there are others I guess were
but I can speak for myself this ma this
insurance company is all over Canada
however this um the location that I
dealt with was in Montreal Quebec Canada
okay uh my I my workplace was in Ontario
please ref free to pause and read as you
go along I'm going to try to go in fast
as possible okay thank
you damages man life is in is
responsible for everything that happen
thereafter because they are part of the
deception okay okay okay so I'm dealing
now with 2018 and this is part two of
three of 2018 I just dealt with part one
this now part two
okay on March 28 2018 man life insurance
for Dr Erin Bon's report Dr James Jang
not to Dr silverberg and requested a
report on a reason why I should remain
off work be for free to pause and read
um oh I need to point out something here
Dr James Chang my family doctor said
that he did not wish to be involved man
life insurance should contact Dr
silverberg The Specialist and not him
after several visits to Dr Sil Dr James
Chang's
office right between March 29 and and
May 22nd he refused each time to provide
a report
okay I think I went
through
um I went through this already in one of
my presentation I think with Belle okay
so I'll be going through quickly all
right as you can see proof the Dr James
Chang receive a report from man life
insurance on March 28 2018 and this was
my return to work and please refe to
read
okay Dr James Shang refused to assist me
please feel free to
read and as you can see here please feel
free to read okay and it says your March
28 this was what I got right and it says
we we received a release from the
assessment firm allowing us to share the
IM um results with Dr Chang um manone
life was deceitful man life wanted me
that is it wanted me to override Dr
silverberg's report by sending a consent
form and uh the consent form would have
um if I had signed it it would have over
ride um overridden Dr silverberg's
report on my assessment to accept Dr
Bon's report who did nothing for me I
refused to sign it and the lawyer wsib
lawyer Adrian nicolini also ignored the
consent form you understand I already
indicated bya form that man life can
communicate with any medical profession
any medical um whether it's hospital or
or or doctor walking Clinic uh um anyone
any Medic in in a medical field that has
anything to do with my injury like if
I've been there for examination or
whatever man life um I signed a content
form already which was still valid but
man life was trying to be smart and I
realize that they don't like smart
people they don't like smart people so I
didn't sign okay but what they did
violated my rights by going to an
assessment firm and
override the um the result for
uh um override the result so that they
could share the the the um what do you
call it the false report the false
report from Dr Erin Bon to Dr James Jang
myself and and Adrian nicolini okay here
it is a copy of the independent medical
examination report was sent to your
attended physician Dr CH dror silverberg
was ignored March 28 so here I
told um Adrian nicolini the lawyer and
he right and then he said I should give
his office a call so he can have a
meeting to discuss be feel free to pause
and read thank
you here Adrian stated idolan on April
fo
2018 FYI you are under no obligation to
return to work okay especially when the
doctor is telling you not to go okay
that said you will not receive a salary
or a short-term disability while we sue
your benefit provider and then please
refe to read
other information
okay on March 28th here it is the
details and then again on on April 20 on
April 12th 2018 from Adel belies she's
not giving up at all she said she has
not yet received anything a copy of the
independent medical examination report
was sent to your attending physician Dr
jown we did not receive a response
further to our to our communication with
your physician sent on March 28 2018 and
notice this is now April 12th so nothing
and I've been going to my doctor okay
each time I get the letter cuz they're
telling me to go back to work I went to
my doctor kept saying doesn't want to be
involved pleas free to pause and read
thank
you I did I I saw Dr James Chang on
April 17th and then um I asked him for
ultrasound he has never from I was
injured from August when I went from I
went to his office in August when he
started swelling on my hand up until
April ail of 2018 from August
right to April
2018 I would say March 2018 right Dr
James Chang has never ever offered to do
examination on my injured hand I was the
one who asked him and when he did when
he actually completed the form when I
saw him on April 17 he actually confused
the the Radiology he actually confused
her I didn't even realize it cuz what he
checked and what he wrote and all that
and then his office was closed on
Wednesday because this was a Tuesday and
I know that um the the 17th was a
Tuesday and the 18th was a Wednesday on
a
Wednesday right they are
not um the office Dr James Str is open
on a Wednesday so they couldn't call him
so they had to do their best in the
ultrasound they did my risk Lon risk
only but still something shows it still
shows that I attend the night is which
was sent to um it was sent to Manny life
but man life still refused it on April
24th Adel stated an Al s report was rece
from your um MD this information cannot
validate your ongoing absence from work
there on April 24th 2018 so it was
refused right a copy of independent
medical examination report was sent to
your attending physician Dr James Chang
we did not receive a response further to
your communication with your physician
sent on March 28th say again April 24th
and still when I went Dr to J on on
April 17 is still refused okay pleas to
pause and
read or it was on this date I would say
here it says Therefore your absent from
work has not is not authorized your
employer will be notified of this okay
time had run out I will show you on the
next page
a view of it I think it says here a
response from your physician and updated
medical information was required by
April 23rd 2018 right and it did the
time had run out it's not to April 24th
so yes they told Belle that my um I am
not authorized to be off work so oh B
started sending the warning letter April
2017 2018 and B Mobility stated that I
should return to my regular work
location okay all right said to dat man
life confirmed that they have not
received any new medical information to
justify an absent from work after April
2nd 2018 okay be free free to pause and
read thank
you okay I went to Great leaks medical
again great leaks as always Great Lakes
at my back Great Lakes Medical okay um
Great Lakes sent U me for an
ultrasound and um on May 1st and the
ultrasound did confirm did everything
correctly and it said it confirmed ten
so I cannot go back to work okay I
provided the information to nicoline
in-law and this is what um he did I
provided in both information in a way
the one from April and one from May to
nicolini Law Firm so he says
nicolini um emailed my supervisor Albert
right on May 1 and then it says it says
as you aware we have been retained to
represent Miss Grant um with respect to
injuries arising out of her disability
he was my diss IB lawyer okay we are in
receipt of Bill correspondence dated
April 7 2018 advising Miss Grant
um is required to come back to work on
May 2nd 2018 as her um Regular to a
regular job we disagree with that
position that's what it said the lawyers
defending me in fact Miss Grant treating
phys specialist Dr silverberg has
confirmed that I returned to her regular
position will only serve to worsen her
um medical condition Dr silverberg
further noted that Miss Grant's um
restrictions um include an inability to
use her right hand repetitively and are
indefinite for the sake of completeness
we have enclosed Dr silverberg um facts
that same physical um report physical
abilities report that it got money life
got on April sorry on February 10th 2018
February 10 2018 right as it the date is
here right confirming the above please
confirm that bill will provide Miss
Grant with modified duties which AC
which accommodate her medically
supported restriction of no
repetitive use of the right hand this
thing in blue here the lawyer mentioned
but I don't know what this is all about
because he did not I guess he just put
it for some reason he did not state
anything like that to me okay please
feel free to pause and read thank
you on May 1st instead of a response
from Albert there was a response from
the lawyer Jessica Reid right and then
he sent it to me he said please see um
see a tatch response with respect to the
above mentioned matter and um Jessica
Reed stated that I'm am acting Council
of B mobility and acknowledge receipt of
email dated May 1st 2018 I will
investigate the matter right so here it
goes now money life iow workplace um
this attachment came right please ref
you to pause and read money life there
was something that I should have showed
you it was um it was I was dealing with
uh the medical doctors at the time they
did an assessment of my work
duties my job uh the job that we do in
our department and they actually said we
had uh 51% idle time idle time this this
report that they brought out on January
25th 2018 the false date because when I
actually got the report someone sent it
to me I recognize what they did the
deception continues CBI workplace
Solutions please feel free to pause and
read if you can this is a fault report
indicating that we have 51% of free
time there were 51 when I got on the
team there were
51 um teammates I was amongst 51
teammates you understand so you can
imagine if we have 51% of free time we
all be sitting doing nothing and we get
good pay we get good pay at B so if B is
s is is if anyone with common sense will
know definitely that this
report is incorrect cuz 51 of us could
not be sitting getting a good pay from B
wa in other words B will be wasting
their their money on us okay feel free
to pause and read if you
can um I did address this already so
because of um man life's deception I was
denied um long-term disability okay I I
there dress address it in B Mobil uh
section there so it's all about Bell
here but because of man life insurance
so showing you that Industrial Alliance
um denied I was denied long-term
disability my um man life owes me for
short-term disability for from April 2nd
up to May 1st because as you can see
they they seize my my benefits from in
um on April
1st April 1st no um
2018 right or April 2nd 2018 April 2nd
2018 and it should have gone up right it
should have ended on May 1st 2018 okay
money life even um indicated the lies to
um Alli Industrial Alliance right about
uh not um my re my reason for not
signing information to Dr silverberg you
understand physical demands analysis I I
could not do that I could not sign that
consent form but anyway please feel free
to pause and review thank you
here I have included the consent this
was a consent form that I had um we I
had completed and submitted which was
submitted to my life okay um it shows
here that I was employed on 8th of June
1998 and it shows that I gave man life
the authorization to ask any medical
company that's involved that I have been
to regarding my injury okay okay be feel
fre to pause and read if you can this
report is the same on the previous slide
okay um I did not receive any calls from
my workplace they stated that they
called I did not receive any calls so on
May 14 2018 the letter stated that um
that to
date they stated that um
we try to contact you but unsuccessfully
landline cell
phone they have both numbers and if they
if if there wasn't a Miss call I would
have seen the Miss calls and I do have
message center they could have left a
message okay so all the the lies
continue they just didn't want to speak
with me but I called Albert the
following day okay the fth the 15th of
May 2018 I call Albert as you can see
the MP3 I I'm I I'm not I've have not
played it I I have the the recorder but
oh for respect um May soul rest in peace
I will not play I will not
play um the MP3 please be free to pause
and
read here there was another response um
uh was submitted to me um by uh Adon
nicolin after he responded to Jessica
regarding Jessica Reed B's lawyer
regarding um how work du is right okay I
actually thought nicolini law was really
in my corner because of his responses
thoughtful responses and all that so on
the 15th of uh of May 2018 right Adan
nicolini responded and he stated that my
reading of the letter right that that
same one about our job duties and stuff
right um so just that at least 49% of
misg Grants shift requires repetitive
use of her right hand so even though
they're saying have idle time still it
was too enough too too much you know
according yeah it was too much right 49%
of M um still requires repetitive use of
her right hand 12% typing and 30 37%
mousing again such a position is
contrary to Dr Silver Bird's restriction
of no repetitive use of her right hand
okay then he said moreover do Dr
silverberg is a treating physician is
treating specialist Who provided a
medical opinion on Miss Grant's
functional abilities based on his
physical examination of her and yes he
did I will not speak listen to this now
lawyer to lawyer here I will not speak
directly to your comment that Dr Erin
Bon is a well-respected
orthopedic surgeon I will note however
that Dr Bon's work is notoriously
one-sided H confirmation and that her
finding have been AC have not been her
findings e have not been accepted at
trial on a number of occasion okay and
then he said in short there is no
obligation to provide Dr
silverberg's um with Dr Bon's report
uhhuh right they want me to still sign a
form so as he said it there's no
obligation I also failed to see how an
ime would change the diagnosis of Mrs
Grant's injury including her functional
restrictions please feel free to pause
and read thank you
okay this is again the report the false
report on our duties all right I will
get to it we will I will get to the
bottom of it the report was not done in
January the report was done in December
remember I said December was at off a
offseason month remember I did say that
in in one of my presentation okay please
feel free to review
okay and on the 15th of May 2018 I said
um because I was still being forced back
to work got something right and it says
hi Adrian yes I am still up this is what
B is doing to me I fall asleep sometimes
3:00 a.m. I did make mention of this um
in one of my other presentation okay so
I don't have to go through it again but
he said um hello Delan your choices
remain the same return to work you
cannot do okay please feel free to pause
and read thank
you here it shows me
um
it it shows here 51% I hope I am not
sure if I'm able to um enlarge it what I
hope I'll you'll be able to see if I can
51% it it indicates it here in the
letter that's what Bell on May 17 2018
when I got my third one letter they are
using that stating I can return to work
because we at 51% of idle time the work
is not demanding demanding our job dut
were analyzed in the month of December
as I did say please feel free to pause
and read
okay oh yes I can okay there it is 51%
of idle time I know things that really
is in their favor but false information
just to get me back to work all right
they still wanted me back in my regular
position okay no
change see presentation on the discrimin
by money life insurance part six with
details of our job duties okay details
of a job
duties here May 14 2018 I was terminated
for my job okay because of manone life
manone life insurance
contributed to my termination from work
okay okay so I was terminated for my job
and Dr James Chang finally sent a
medical report but two months late it
was two months late and I was terminated
for my job on May 24th but he sent the
report on May 25th I already went
through this with you on another
presentation I will just go through
quickly please feele free to pause and
read
okay we're already aware of March 28th
from ever since he got the report all
right and he just on May 25th 2018
that's when he did responded via letter
and he the report some information are
are true but he was doing it to cover
himself some things were biased within
his report okay please feel free to
pause and read thank
you and again I included Clarity so you
can
see everything here okay I did address
this matter in my report on B Mobility
uh yes so please feel free to pause and
read I didn't know it was because of U
man life insurance Dr James CH refuse to
assist okay all right so please be free
to pause and read confirm that I still
add decran
tenosinovitis okay please free free okay
I'm repeating
myself
okay on this um for this section here as
uh as I um included part page three of
Dr James Chang's report as you can see
um the doctor said I was last seen on
May 3rd
okay no to take care of her wrist
problem see I have a I had a wrist
problem okay and uh on May E I actually
saw Dr Chang my last day was on May 26
second and I and I and this time I I
shed tears I wasn't going on carrying on
it hysterically or anything I just I was
a shedding tears just rolling down my
eyes and I said doc please I got my
final warning letter please I don't want
to lose my job you know playing to my
doctor and he still
refused yeah you still refused my doctor
was actually giving me a prescription he
actually asked me to fill up the form
and then it he looked at it and say oh
delene um you are depressed so then he
was giving me a prescription and I said
come on Doc come
on when did you have you seen me like
this before isn't it natural for me to
be depressed I'm about to lose my job if
I'd come into your office being happy
and and oh dog and laughing I'm about to
lose my job and thing you think that I'm
crazy but isn't
it human of me to shed tear because I'm
about to lose my job of 20 years and
when I fill out that form it's all my
I'm feeling at the moment I'm feeling at
the moment because I'm really sad
because you're not assisting me I've
been coming to you for March
right and I refused to take that
prescription because I know I was not
mental however as you can see here on
that day the 22nd of May they have me
with mental thing imagine if I taken
that if I Tak that description or and
fill that description the system would
actually had me as really being mental I
am not mental okay it is to me this is
human when we are hurt that is how we
act okay wow anyway please feel free to
pause and read thank
you this as I said I extracted from the
Ministry of Health System everyone come
came together all
right damages man life insurance and IND
Alliance short-term disability and
long-term disability man life is
short-term disability and the Industrial
Alliance is long-term disability just
spare that in mind
okay this is proof that manone life
insurance right owes one month
short-term disability man life insurance
um prematurely suspended my short-term
disability benefits on April 2nd 2018
right and as you can have um as you can
see here
my Industrial Alliance indicated your
short-term disability cycle will be
ended on May 1st
2018 April 2nd 2018 should have ended on
May 1st
um so man life owes for one month right
short-term disability and because of
whatever um information man in life
passed on to B Mobility right and or I
don't know Industrial Alliance I was
denied long-term disability so I still
have my injury so Industrial Alliance
owes
for as of um May 2nd 2018 owes for
long-term disability okay to present
please refe to pause and read and that
I'll see you over on um part three of
2018 thank
you